Guide to the Joseph Follet papers, 1874-1916.
Follet, Joseph papers, 1874-1916.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Joseph Follet papers, 1874-1916.
3882
Joseph Follet, d. 1879.
.2 cubic ft.
Letters.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection includes letters, certificates of discharge, and memorial cards. Letters from Follett, who was lost at sea in 1879, are to Annie Fearn, whom he married in 1878, concerning his health, the weather, and a little information about ports and cargoes; mass cards are those of Joseph and Harry Follett, who died in 1881; certificate of marriage of Fearn and Follett; petition for Exempt Certificate (1916) for Joe Follett; also, letters concerning the wages and effects of Follett due Annie, and an unsigned letter.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
British ship steward and cook.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection includes letters, certificates of discharge, and memorial cards. Letters from Follett, who was lost at sea in 1879, are to Annie Fearn, whom he married in 1878, concerning his health, the weather, and a little information about ports and cargoes; mass cards are those of Joseph and Harry Follett, who died in 1881; certificate of marriage of Fearn and Follett; petition for Exempt Certificate (1916) for Joe Follett; also, letters concerning the wages and effects of Follett due Annie, and an unsigned letter.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Follet, Joseph, d. 1879.; Fearn, Annie.; Follett, Harry.; Follett, Joe.
Subjects:
Seafaring life.; Sailors.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Photocopies
  - 1874 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1875 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1876 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1877 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1878 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1879, 1881, 1886, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Originals
  - 1874 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1875 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1876 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1877-1879, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)